heateor.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy - Heateor

### What Information We Collect

  * We **do not** collect you personal information, except your email address (minimum required information) which is required in checkout process to send details regarding the purchase. We may use this email address to contact you in future regrading updates of the add-on(s) you purchase,  **only  in the worst case scenario** when it is not possible to provide automatic updates (due to technical reasons)
  * Server log information, such as – **Web Requests** , **Internet Protocol Address** , **Browser and System Information**
  * We use cookies to save products in shopping cart
  * We send the Facebook Comment you post, to website administrator via automated email, only from your consent that you grant before posting Facebook Comment at our website. This data includes just the Facebook comment posted by you

### Third Party Widgets

  * We embed Facebook Comments plugin to allow you to leave reviews at our website using your Facebook account. This plugin may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the commenting interface, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the interface (such as “liking” someone’s comment, replying to other comments), if you are logged into Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update
  * We use GooglePlus Comments widget at our Heateor Social Comments Demo page for you to be able to comment there using your GooglePlus account. From this interaction Google automatically collects and store certain information in server logs like IP address, device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy
  * We use Disqus Comments widget at our Heateor Social Comments Demo page for you to be able to comment there using Disqus commenting system. Disqus may collect information about you when you register for and use the Service. Such information may include “Personally Identifiable Information” which means information that identifies you as an individual, such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, telephone number, username or account ID, and “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” which means information that does not identify you as an individual. Non-Personally Identifiable Information may include, but is not limited to, information about your browser, your IP address, device ID, what pages you visit on our Partner Sites, which website you came from, what advertisements you clicked on, whether on our Partner Websites, the Service or other third party websites, and other information about your online activity that does not identify you as an individual, in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy

### What Information We Share

  * We **do not** share Personally Identifiable Information (PII) with anyone
  * We may share non-personal information, such as – Software and system specifications, other non-personal data

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy by posting a new version on our website. This helps you to always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed.

### Furthermore

If you have any questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at **privacy [at] heateor [dot] com**
